Jhal
you should study
he says that I have requested my heart there are
some things which we do not do to be equal
like I do not leave office early
otherwise people will say that she was a girl and has gone away there is
this rumour in Punjab
do it
or not
quiz on
[Music]
but the people of 350
areas can never go back to school
thinking about this I study a little more every inch of the way
what happened I should not miss my father that is why
sometimes I make Mohan Bhagwat Katha of mother
[Music]
Rajesh just because he fulfils it he
tells everyone Shivratri festival Pranav instead of the
other part remembering this fact
that when you do a little more to be equal then you should do
more too
milk ashwagandha and rectangle from this plane
promise yourself that you will definitely improve your standards
ICICI Lombard wish you happy
birthday do it
to Ajay